<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Women on Butterfly Dream</title>
    <link>http://abijango.com/tags/women/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Women on Butterfly Dream</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://abijango.com/tags/women/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sacrifice</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-19-sacrifice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-19-sacrifice/</guid>
      <description>Women All of what is written in the linked article is true, women are generally expected to make all the sacrifices for a marriage; or more accurately, trained to believe to give up all their hopes and dreams and live according to the lives their husbands choose for them.
And no matter how much we want it to be not true, it is. Even the modern woman feels the pressure from family and society to conform to these social norms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing a Husband</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-18-sharing-a-husband/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-18-sharing-a-husband/</guid>
      <description>Got linked to this article on Facebook. What an insane story of intelligence and wisom displayed by a maid.
Granted their situation was a difficult one, and it is all on the in-laws of the widow who gave her so much difficulty in the first place, but it is inspiring to know that there are brave and intelligent people out in the world.
The problem of the widow can be summed up in this one sentence:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The abuse of labour</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-27-abuse-of-labour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-27-abuse-of-labour/</guid>
      <description>When we talk about abuses of women and generally labour in our country we cry foul at all stages. Women are abused, downtrodden and generally not held in the highest regard in our society. Not taking anything away from those abuses, they are horrible in their own right. But today I wanted to just talk about the post over at BBC that I read a while back. Namely, the abuse of women in Melilla, and specifically their abuse as mules for transport of goods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My take on Woman, thy place is at home</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/2013/09/28/woman-thy-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/2013/09/28/woman-thy-place/</guid>
      <description>I read an article over at Messy Thoughts which I think is an excellent take on the issue of &amp;lsquo;useless education&amp;rsquo;. Go ahead read it first and come back, I&amp;rsquo;ll wait.
I am totally for education itself and improving oneself, but to get a degree and not use it, is an insult to education itself. Maybe you say, it is their own (or their parent&amp;rsquo;s atleast) money, and it is for them to do with as they will.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>