<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pakistan on Butterfly Dream</title>
    <link>http://abijango.com/tags/pakistan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pakistan on Butterfly Dream</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://abijango.com/tags/pakistan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Censorship</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-03-24-censorship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-03-24-censorship/</guid>
      <description>Stories like these might sound sensational to you. Yes they are trying to paint a very bleak picture of our society and the kind of censorship that is prevalent. But it doesn&amp;rsquo;t change the fact that it is censorship.
 Today&amp;rsquo;s edition of The International New York Times was stripped of its cover story in Pakistan. Instead of seeing a lengthy report on &amp;ldquo;What Pakistan knew about bin Laden,&amp;rdquo; readers were greeted with an enormous section of white space that dominates the paper&amp;rsquo;s front page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sacrifice</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-19-sacrifice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-19-sacrifice/</guid>
      <description>Women All of what is written in the linked article is true, women are generally expected to make all the sacrifices for a marriage; or more accurately, trained to believe to give up all their hopes and dreams and live according to the lives their husbands choose for them.
And no matter how much we want it to be not true, it is. Even the modern woman feels the pressure from family and society to conform to these social norms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tolerance, or lack thereof</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-18-tolerance-or-lack-thereof/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-18-tolerance-or-lack-thereof/</guid>
      <description>Well written article over at the Tribune. I especially like the fact that the write starts to explain what her interpretation of the events of Karballa were, then leaves them out, as that is not what the post was about. It was about one thing, tolerance.
We pride ourselves in being Muslims, followers of the best religion known to mankind. And yet we are the scum of the earth. If something our our religion had actually gone through our goddamn thick skulls we would respect our fellow man&amp;rsquo;s difference of opinion and let them live their lives in peace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State and Religion: The Need for Seperation</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-08-state-and-religion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-08-state-and-religion/</guid>
      <description>So following a discussion on a social media that-must-not-be-named (mainly because I hate it), I decided that a post on my opinions on the matter of State and Religion, or their seperate; was in order.
##Duties of the State
To begin this, let us first think about what the state actually means or what it is supposed to mean/do.
The responsibilities of the state can be broadly described as1:
 Protection: Ensure the safety of the people/citizens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pakistan</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-25-pakistan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-25-pakistan/</guid>
      <description>Granted I do not reside in the country of my birth anymore, nor have I for the last 5 years. A lot of arguments have been made to me in this regard.
Pakistan is not the same as you remember it to be.
Thinks have changed.
And so on.
Granted those arguments are valid. And the reasons for which I left my country are still valid to this day from when I left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the NUST fines/issues</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-01-on-this-new-nust-drama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-01-on-this-new-nust-drama/</guid>
      <description>I will start this by saying I attended E&amp;amp;ME College, NUST from 2003-2007. Hence, I have a very personal taste on these issues that everyone is talking about. To get it out of the way, EM&amp;amp;E College, NUST was a horrible place to study. Simply terri-bad. I have spent years of my life after my time there trying to erase it from my memory. Granted I met some of my best friends in that university, but most if not all friendships were based on our mutual hatred of EM&amp;amp;E and its administration.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>