<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Butterfly Dream</title>
    <link>http://abijango.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Butterfly Dream</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 11:29:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://abijango.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Oldest Star Wars Fan</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-11-27-the-oldest-star-wars-fan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 11:29:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-11-27-the-oldest-star-wars-fan/</guid>
      <description>The first guy who ever realised what a success Star Wars was going to be. Just before the new movie comes out, and people still bashing Star Wars. Eat your hearts out haters!
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leonard Nimoy, dies at 83</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-27-leonard-nimoy-dies-at-83/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-27-leonard-nimoy-dies-at-83/</guid>
      <description>A legend dies. Seriously all, &amp;ldquo;Live long, and prosper!&amp;rdquo; \\// :(
 &amp;ldquo;Given the choice,&amp;rdquo; he wrote, &amp;ldquo;if I had to be someone else, I would be Spock.&amp;rdquo;
 You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Boba Fett Escaped the Sarlacc Pit</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-23-boba-fetts-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-23-boba-fetts-escape/</guid>
      <description>Where a fan goes the extra mile:
 Stoefller submitted the diorama for French lego contest, along with a fantastical story that offers an alternate take on how Boba survived falling into the Sarlacc during Return of the Jedi.
 The detail is just astonishing.
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sale of the Original Les Paul Black Beauty</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-23-original-les-paul-black-beauty-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-23-original-les-paul-black-beauty-sale/</guid>
      <description>Holy shit! If only I had that kind of money. Gief!
 Les Paul&amp;rsquo;s personal 1954 Les Paul Custom &amp;ldquo;Black Beauty&amp;rdquo; sold to Indianapolis Colts owner Jim Irsay last night for $343,750.
 You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heroes Reborn Teaser</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-04-heroes-reborn-teaser/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-04-heroes-reborn-teaser/</guid>
      <description>I know what people say about Heroes, and no I won&amp;rsquo;t link to them. Who cares, I loved that show. And sadto see some of the original cast won&amp;rsquo;t be (and glad about some, I hated Claire&amp;rsquo;s character) but seriously watch the teaser, DAMN!
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Madame Tussauds Star Wars Exhibition</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-04-madame-tussauds-star-wars-exhibition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-04-madame-tussauds-star-wars-exhibition/</guid>
      <description>On the back of so much Star Wars talk this week, here is some more, Madam Tussauds will open a Star Wars exhibition this year. Holy shit. Ok so since it is only a short walk from my office, I am probably wasting a lot of money there. DAMNIT! SHUTUP AND TAKE MY MONEY!
 Opening May 2015 Madame Tussauds London will take you to your favourite Star Wars scenes. Star Wars at Madame Tussauds will be a unique, immersive experience featuring 16 of the most famous heroes and villains in scenes from some of the most iconic moments featured in Star Wars Episodes I – VI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix&#39;s Daredevil Teaser</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-04-netflix-daredevil-teaser/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-04-netflix-daredevil-teaser/</guid>
      <description>Daredevil heads to the tv screen! And it is bloody! Let&amp;rsquo;s hope it can make us forget all about that bad, bad movie. Yes you know which one I am talking about. You have just removed it from your memory.
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Brief History of Star Wars Canon</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-03-brief-history-of-star-wars-canon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-03-brief-history-of-star-wars-canon/</guid>
      <description>Star Wars has always had a special place in my heart. I write and tweet about it a lot. Maybe too much.
Nah!
After I had devoured the movies over and over again as a kid, I was left hanging. I wanted more. I wanted the Episodes I-III (OK maybe in hindsight I should have been careful what I wished for!), and there was nothing. I am sure it was much worse for the people for whom Star Wars had been a part of their lives since the late 70&amp;rsquo;s and 80&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>50 Years of James Bond in Black Tie</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-01-30-fifty-years-of-bond-in-black-tie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-01-30-fifty-years-of-bond-in-black-tie/</guid>
      <description>What a really thourough investigation. Every single piece of clothing (no shoes sadly) calatalogued. The little nerd in me wants to do re-runs now (No Timothy Dalton, no way!).
 Though there are 28 dinner jackets, there are 29 shirts. George Lazenby wears two different ruffled shirts with the same dinner jacket in On Her Majesty’s Secret Service. Also, shoes are unfortunately missing from this infographic since they are rarely seen in the films.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zakk Wylde&#39;s Audio Gear</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-01-30-zakk-wyldes-audio-gear/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-01-30-zakk-wyldes-audio-gear/</guid>
      <description>Just shut up and take my money! If I had any that is. When this stuff comes out.
 Time will tell if Wylde will GIFD &amp;ndash; the acronym for &amp;ldquo;get it f&amp;ndash;ing done&amp;rdquo; that he and his BLS brethren have adopted as a motto.
 You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The paintings of the Original Star Wars Trilogy</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-01-29-star-wars-paintings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-01-29-star-wars-paintings/</guid>
      <description>Talk about a childhood destroyed. I always thought they created this somehow, miniatures or something. But paintings? Wow!
 Matte paintings are fake sets that—most of the times—used to be made with plexiglass and oil paint. The artists used oversized panels to create the necessary detail that the camera needed to fool the audiences when the film was projected over the large surface of the theater screen. The paintings were combined with live action filmed to match the perspective of the painting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Protests</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-09-29-hong-kong-protests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-09-29-hong-kong-protests/</guid>
      <description>Pro-democracy riots in Hong Kong. Note the similarities in the police actions and the reactions by the public to what is recently happening back home in Pakistan.
 The government urdged the protesters to end their sit-in demonstrations.
 Now why would people do that? Why is it that everywhere protests start &amp;ndash; Pakistan, UK, Hong Kong, elsewhere &amp;ndash; the authorities always have their ridiculous demands about not protesting? Why? Other than the authourities, who else benifits from not protesting?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Avellone&#39;s Gaming Rig</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-09-25-chris-avellones-gaming-rig/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-09-25-chris-avellones-gaming-rig/</guid>
      <description>Chris Avellone has been one of my childhood heroes since a friend of mine told me to go read the credits on our favourite game of all time, Fallout 2. Him and the other&amp;rsquo;s who made the amazing games over at Black Isle Studios just made my childhood amazing.
I now get to see a loot at what he uses as a gaming machine and his general desk and place of work/fun, great insight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For less than the price of a Hollywood movie</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-09-25-for-less-than-gravity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-09-25-for-less-than-gravity/</guid>
      <description>I wrote about India&amp;rsquo;s mission to Mars a while back, and now that spaceship has finally reached Mar&amp;rsquo;s orbit.
And all of this for less than the cost of what it took to make Gravity.
I think the New York Time&amp;rsquo;s article say&amp;rsquo;s it best though.
 One a shoestring, India sends orbiter to Mars on it&amp;rsquo;s first try.
 The trip cost India $74 million. Gravity on the other hand cost $100 million.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Censorship</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-03-24-censorship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-03-24-censorship/</guid>
      <description>Stories like these might sound sensational to you. Yes they are trying to paint a very bleak picture of our society and the kind of censorship that is prevalent. But it doesn&amp;rsquo;t change the fact that it is censorship.
 Today&amp;rsquo;s edition of The International New York Times was stripped of its cover story in Pakistan. Instead of seeing a lengthy report on &amp;ldquo;What Pakistan knew about bin Laden,&amp;rdquo; readers were greeted with an enormous section of white space that dominates the paper&amp;rsquo;s front page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fight Club in 2 minutes</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-03-10-fight-club-in-2-minutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-03-10-fight-club-in-2-minutes/</guid>
      <description>Fight Club is, and always will be one of my favourite movies. Call it a hunger for violence, or a passion for dark gritty stories. I don&amp;rsquo;t care, I love this movie. And for you who can&amp;rsquo;t stand the original because of its violence (I pity you!), go ahead and watch this 2 minute version.
It blends the original story with the classic Sega games like Streets of Rage style graphics, classic!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the World Wars inspired the Millennium Falcon</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-21-millennium-falcon-and-the-world-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-21-millennium-falcon-and-the-world-wars/</guid>
      <description>The Millennium Falcon is no doubt some of the most recognizable nerd craft. The article traces the inspirations:
 The connections begin in the cockpit of the Falcon with its iconic greenhouse-style window. It was here that audiences first jumped to hyperspace, and from these famous viewports that Han Solo evaded Imperial ships in the asteroid field above Hoth. Thirty years earlier, this same style of cockpit was found flying aboard one of the most advanced bomber aircraft of World War II: The American B-29 Superfortress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lego Movie</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-20-the-lego-movie/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-20-the-lego-movie/</guid>
      <description>With a 96% critics rating and a 92% audience rating, you know this movie has done something right. It is a family movie, so go in obviously expecting that. But given that, I enjoyed it more than I ever imagined.
The little details, the references. The way the references were handled, even the overall main and underlying stories; typical as they were, were pretty good. Not all entertainment needs to be vulgar to make it big.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>House of Cards and China</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-19-house-of-cards-and-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-19-house-of-cards-and-china/</guid>
      <description>Many of you watch this series, and many of you love it. It may be the acting or the overly dramatized politics. There is no doubt House of Cards is a very popular series, not even going into how amazing it is that Netflix is making such amazing original content, as that is a whole seperate post; let&amp;rsquo;s talk about its popularity abroad.
To say Chinese people get the wrong idea of American politics by watching this series is again a half statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sacrifice</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-19-sacrifice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-19-sacrifice/</guid>
      <description>Women All of what is written in the linked article is true, women are generally expected to make all the sacrifices for a marriage; or more accurately, trained to believe to give up all their hopes and dreams and live according to the lives their husbands choose for them.
And no matter how much we want it to be not true, it is. Even the modern woman feels the pressure from family and society to conform to these social norms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gotham</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-12-gotham-the-series/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-12-gotham-the-series/</guid>
      <description>As we all know, anything to do with Batman gets me excited. Being as they are about to mutilate the origin story once again, I have some very strong thoughts on the matter. Which also brings me to the linked article:
 Here’s what I WOULDN’T do in the pilot: Kill Thomas and Martha Wayne.
 Yes, yes we all know that is the defining moment in Bruce&amp;rsquo;s career to becoming Batman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Life is a Game</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-06-life-is-a-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-06-life-is-a-game/</guid>
      <description>Wish someone had shared that with me when I was much much younger.
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars Episode VII script complete</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-01-20-star-wars-episode-7-script-complete/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-01-20-star-wars-episode-7-script-complete/</guid>
      <description>I am just hoping they don&amp;rsquo;t screw it up rushing it, but I guess Disney is just seeing the $$$$ and not much else.
That said, I can&amp;rsquo;t fucking wait!
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Burger&#39;s Guide to Islamabad</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-01-09-burgers-guide-to-islamabad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-01-09-burgers-guide-to-islamabad/</guid>
      <description>Absolutely hilarious. I love my hometown, and yes before you ask, it IS better than its twin city. Love how the writer illustrates the different divides within the city with such humour.
There are always comparions made by Lahori-ites and Karachi-ites about how their cities have so much happening, and Islamabad is boring and lame and all that. To that I would like to quote a friend, &amp;ldquo;Jealous not, Darrrlinnnggg!!&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Iron Man made of Lego?</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-01-09-iron-man-is-made-of-lego/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-01-09-iron-man-is-made-of-lego/</guid>
      <description>So it seems like Tony Stark is also a fan of Lego. Or his captors are? In either case it is always pretty funny when movies/series use code copied from somewhere, but in this case it looks like one of the designers had a sense of humour.
 The code above comes from a firmware downloader for the RCX (a programmable, microcontroller-based Lego brick), written in 1998 at Stanford University by Kekoa Proudfoot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Official Star Wars Universe Just...Expanded</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-01-08-star-wars-expanded-universe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-01-08-star-wars-expanded-universe/</guid>
      <description>So this just basically means that the new movies could draw their inspiration from some of the richest stories ever told in science fiction. Hell yes!
Here&amp;rsquo;s to hoping Disney picks up on the nerdgasms this has generated in the Star Wars community and decide to actually pick some of the most amazing story lines for the upcoming movies or animated series/films.
 So if by Episode VIII fans meet Grand Admiral Thrawn, all the better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finally an answer to: How long is the Runway in Fast 6?</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-12-31-how-long-is-the-runway/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-12-31-how-long-is-the-runway/</guid>
      <description>Totally useless bit of information, but it has nagged me since I saw the movie. My estimates were around ~26km, accounting for the scenes that could have taken place in parallel. Seems like the guys over in BBC had the same idea.
 Our best estimate after calculating plane speed, car speed and simultaneous action sequences is that the runway is 18.37 miles (29.6km) long. Which is still very long when you consider the longest paved runway in the world is the Qamdo Bamda airport in China, at around 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Lambert&#39;s Art on an iPad</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-12-03-art-on-an-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-12-03-art-on-an-ipad/</guid>
      <description>I do experiment a little with Paper by 53 from time to time, actually this blog is sort of inspired by the man Michael Rose himself. I also sketch traditionally sometimes, have for many years; but looking at this, I am blown away. The patience and skill required to do something like this is just staggering. I wish one day I will have even a 10th of what Kyle has.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Amazon Way</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-12-02-the-amazon-way/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-12-02-the-amazon-way/</guid>
      <description>Amazing interview. From the scale of Amazon&amp;rsquo;s operations, to the forward thinking ideas (some very sci-fi), and just the general philosophy. Jeff Bezos:
 Jeff Bezos: The long term approach is rare enough that it means you&amp;rsquo;re not competing against very many companies. &amp;lsquo;Cause most companies wanna see a return on investment in, you know, one, two, three years.
Charlie Rose: You don’t care about that?
Jeff Bezos: I care, but I&amp;rsquo;m willing for it to be five, six, seven years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logic in Religion</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-19-logic-in-religion/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-19-logic-in-religion/</guid>
      <description>I read a very thought provoking post over at Messy Thoughts and the following discussion regarding the post was insanely entertaining. Lots of self-righteousness rearing its ugly head and all that fun stuff.
Let me go over into a rant on the subject now. I have been contemplating this whole idea about Religion and Logic and blind-faith and all that stuff for a long time. I am very thankful that I had a grandfather who was very challenging in this regard, always made me question everything and always said:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Even the Pentagon can get away with fraud</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-18-pentagon-and-fraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-18-pentagon-and-fraud/</guid>
      <description>Hahahahahahaha.
Ok enough making fun of the situation (not really!). We can all point fingers, but the fact of the matter is, this is extremely sad.
Quick quote:
 &amp;ldquo;The Army lost track of roughly $5.8 billion worth of supplies between 2003 and 2011.&amp;rdquo;
 Kind of reminds me of another army.
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sharing a Husband</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-18-sharing-a-husband/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-18-sharing-a-husband/</guid>
      <description>Got linked to this article on Facebook. What an insane story of intelligence and wisom displayed by a maid.
Granted their situation was a difficult one, and it is all on the in-laws of the widow who gave her so much difficulty in the first place, but it is inspiring to know that there are brave and intelligent people out in the world.
The problem of the widow can be summed up in this one sentence:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tolerance, or lack thereof</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-18-tolerance-or-lack-thereof/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-18-tolerance-or-lack-thereof/</guid>
      <description>Well written article over at the Tribune. I especially like the fact that the write starts to explain what her interpretation of the events of Karballa were, then leaves them out, as that is not what the post was about. It was about one thing, tolerance.
We pride ourselves in being Muslims, followers of the best religion known to mankind. And yet we are the scum of the earth. If something our our religion had actually gone through our goddamn thick skulls we would respect our fellow man&amp;rsquo;s difference of opinion and let them live their lives in peace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The BatKid Story</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-17-the-batkid-story/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-17-the-batkid-story/</guid>
      <description>The internet is flush with articles on the BatKid story.
 &amp;ldquo;The Make-A-Wish Foundation has often arranged elaborate gifts for kids with life-threatening diseases - but never at this scale&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;We were here to cheer on Miles, but Miles also helped us&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo;
 Stories like these start to restore my faith in humanity, but then there are always the naysayers:
 Not everyone felt the love. While city police officials said they handled Friday&amp;rsquo;s crowds without extra staffing or costs, some thought the event focused too much energy on one child.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Abuses in Orthodox Communities</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-14-the-abuses-in-orthodox-communities/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-14-the-abuses-in-orthodox-communities/</guid>
      <description>Disclaimer: The link post and the following article is extremely graphic. Read at your own risk.
There have been countless stories of abuse in our society, and reading this post, I wanted to highlight how it&amp;rsquo;s not just us who have this problem; but the cases are highly similar as are their outcomes. The absolutely disgusting behavior occurs everywhere, and though we are no stranger to such stories, it is still worth discussion in my opinion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Poetry of Life</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-13-the-poetry-of-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-13-the-poetry-of-life/</guid>
      <description>I have been thinking a lot about the current state of my life. How much time I spend working, and the whole &amp;lsquo;work-life balance issue&amp;rsquo;. Personally, as a lot of others have stated before as well, I believe the whole term &amp;lsquo;work-life balance&amp;rsquo; is flawed.
As the argument goes, work is part of life, not a separate entity. And we consider life to be worth a lot less than work. After all you need to work to make a living right?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State and Religion: The Need for Seperation</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-08-state-and-religion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-08-state-and-religion/</guid>
      <description>So following a discussion on a social media that-must-not-be-named (mainly because I hate it), I decided that a post on my opinions on the matter of State and Religion, or their seperate; was in order.
##Duties of the State
To begin this, let us first think about what the state actually means or what it is supposed to mean/do.
The responsibilities of the state can be broadly described as1:
 Protection: Ensure the safety of the people/citizens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alcohol the Deadly Sin</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-07-alcohol-the-deadly-sin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-07-alcohol-the-deadly-sin/</guid>
      <description>Having lived in a western country for the last 5 years, maybe my views have changed on the matter. Then again, they might have just been solidified.
I have no problem with the consumption of alcohol, by a non-muslim or by a muslim. Where I have a problem with, is intoxication and the resulting stupidity that ensues. And then again, that is a personal opinion. I am glad to be living in a country where a &amp;lsquo;majority&amp;rsquo; of people won&amp;rsquo;t moan at me for my personal opinions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Close Encounters of the Married Kind</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-07-close-encounters-of-the-married-kind/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-07-close-encounters-of-the-married-kind/</guid>
      <description>A good friend of mine writes these hilarious stories about a &amp;lsquo;fictional&amp;rsquo; husband and wife and their &amp;lsquo;totally made-up stories&amp;rsquo; :).
Worth a read!
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discussion</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-07-discussion/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-07-discussion/</guid>
      <description>I am getting a lot of personal one-to-one feedback on the posts which is great. Just to remind you, if you want to shout at me, argue, or just have a plain discussion, all the links are in the About section. Top menu -&amp;gt; About.
I do reply to emails etc. but by far the best place to have a discussion is Twitter.
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Jekyll Setup and related things - Part 1</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-06-setup-and-other-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-06-setup-and-other-things/</guid>
      <description>I think finally I would like to write about how this blog is set up, for all you geeks out there, I am sure you might enjoy this.
So let us begin!
Jekyll and all that Jekyll, is a simple static blogging system, or as they say, blogging for hackers. Basically, it eliminates the database from the backend. All that is there is your content (posts) and that is it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So you like Star Wars?</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-06-star-wars-audition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-06-star-wars-audition/</guid>
      <description>So they are looking for two roles:
 They are a &amp;ldquo;street smart and strong&amp;rdquo; orphaned girl in her late teens and a &amp;ldquo;smart capable&amp;rdquo; man in his late teens or early 20s.
 So let&amp;rsquo;s all go and audition for these roles? If only&amp;hellip;.
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feedback</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-01-feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-01-feedback/</guid>
      <description>So I have had some feedback from some of you who have read the recent posts (I know they are not a lot). And it has been most helpful.
Basic points that came out of the feedback are summarised as follows:
 Injustice posts seem to be mostly rambling. I understand that these are first drafts that were mainly published to get feedback from you guys in the first place, but that does not excuse bad quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The abuse of labour</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-27-abuse-of-labour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-27-abuse-of-labour/</guid>
      <description>When we talk about abuses of women and generally labour in our country we cry foul at all stages. Women are abused, downtrodden and generally not held in the highest regard in our society. Not taking anything away from those abuses, they are horrible in their own right. But today I wanted to just talk about the post over at BBC that I read a while back. Namely, the abuse of women in Melilla, and specifically their abuse as mules for transport of goods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pakistan</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-25-pakistan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-25-pakistan/</guid>
      <description>Granted I do not reside in the country of my birth anymore, nor have I for the last 5 years. A lot of arguments have been made to me in this regard.
Pakistan is not the same as you remember it to be.
Thinks have changed.
And so on.
Granted those arguments are valid. And the reasons for which I left my country are still valid to this day from when I left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On India&#39;s Mission to Mars</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-22-indias-mission-to-mars/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-22-indias-mission-to-mars/</guid>
      <description>Our neighbours over in India have a plan to launch a space mission to Mars.
 The Mangalyaan probe was to have been launched as early as 28 October, but rough weather in the Pacific forced officials to delay the launch by a week. The unmanned mission has a launch window lasting until 19 November.
 Meanwhile in Pakistan we still concern ourselves with useless issues like what our Northern province should be called?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RSS and other improvements</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-21-rss-and-other-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-21-rss-and-other-things/</guid>
      <description>I finally got RSS to work on the site, along with a few other under the hood improvements.
To point the RSS to your favourite Google Reader replacement, please go to the menu bar at the top -&amp;gt; RSS. Or point it directly to http://abijango.com/feed if you want.
I have some further enhancements in the pipeline, which will be rolling out sooner or later.
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Injustice for All: A Little South of Sanity</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-16-little-south-of-sanity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-16-little-south-of-sanity/</guid>
      <description>The laughter is the first thing that gets to most people. The shriekers, the wailers. And then those who snicker as if they know something you don&amp;rsquo;t. Makes more than a few wonder if it&amp;rsquo;s in fact the patients who know more than you. That they are privy to secrets that you are not. Maybe feeling that way is what drives most people away from places like this. An asylum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Injustice for All: Dusty Neighbourhood</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-14-dusty-neighbourhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-14-dusty-neighbourhood/</guid>
      <description>Flicking the cigarette and taking a swig from the half drunk cup of coffee, he sighed. Out came the smoke in misty curls. He half tried to make rings, failed miserably and gave up. He was never very good at that. Looking out the window to his scenic view, the first thing that you saw was the criss-crossed wires. Telephone wires, electricity wires, bloody everything else wires. Covered in dirt and bird shit and god knows what else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Injustice for All</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-02-injustice-for-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-02-injustice-for-all/</guid>
      <description>I have been writing short stories since I was very young. Most of them used to be nothing more than just childhood fiction. These days I am more interested in writing about certain aspects of my culture. Highlighting certain issues if you will.
The future posts that follow with the titles beginning with &amp;ldquo;Injustice for All&amp;rdquo;, will be part of short stories that are linked in one way or another; and where I try to fit together these disjointed stories about things that I want to highlight about my culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the NUST fines/issues</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-01-on-this-new-nust-drama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-01-on-this-new-nust-drama/</guid>
      <description>I will start this by saying I attended E&amp;amp;ME College, NUST from 2003-2007. Hence, I have a very personal taste on these issues that everyone is talking about. To get it out of the way, EM&amp;amp;E College, NUST was a horrible place to study. Simply terri-bad. I have spent years of my life after my time there trying to erase it from my memory. Granted I met some of my best friends in that university, but most if not all friendships were based on our mutual hatred of EM&amp;amp;E and its administration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My take on Woman, thy place is at home</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/2013/09/28/woman-thy-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/2013/09/28/woman-thy-place/</guid>
      <description>I read an article over at Messy Thoughts which I think is an excellent take on the issue of &amp;lsquo;useless education&amp;rsquo;. Go ahead read it first and come back, I&amp;rsquo;ll wait.
I am totally for education itself and improving oneself, but to get a degree and not use it, is an insult to education itself. Maybe you say, it is their own (or their parent&amp;rsquo;s atleast) money, and it is for them to do with as they will.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Blank Page</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-09-26-the-blank-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-09-26-the-blank-page/</guid>
      <description>I will begin this by saying I am not a writer. I have always wanted to be able to write well, but never had the drive or the energy to go ahead and do it. This blog is finally a first step in the journey to becoming a better writer.
As such, this will be a collection of all the small titbits I write, along with links and my personal comments on the articles I find interesting and those that make it to my reading lists.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>