<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Politics on Butterfly Dream</title>
    <link>http://abijango.com/tags/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Politics on Butterfly Dream</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://abijango.com/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Protests</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-09-29-hong-kong-protests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-09-29-hong-kong-protests/</guid>
      <description>Pro-democracy riots in Hong Kong. Note the similarities in the police actions and the reactions by the public to what is recently happening back home in Pakistan.
 The government urdged the protesters to end their sit-in demonstrations.
 Now why would people do that? Why is it that everywhere protests start &amp;ndash; Pakistan, UK, Hong Kong, elsewhere &amp;ndash; the authorities always have their ridiculous demands about not protesting? Why? Other than the authourities, who else benifits from not protesting?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>House of Cards and China</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-19-house-of-cards-and-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-19-house-of-cards-and-china/</guid>
      <description>Many of you watch this series, and many of you love it. It may be the acting or the overly dramatized politics. There is no doubt House of Cards is a very popular series, not even going into how amazing it is that Netflix is making such amazing original content, as that is a whole seperate post; let&amp;rsquo;s talk about its popularity abroad.
To say Chinese people get the wrong idea of American politics by watching this series is again a half statement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On India&#39;s Mission to Mars</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-22-indias-mission-to-mars/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-22-indias-mission-to-mars/</guid>
      <description>Our neighbours over in India have a plan to launch a space mission to Mars.
 The Mangalyaan probe was to have been launched as early as 28 October, but rough weather in the Pacific forced officials to delay the launch by a week. The unmanned mission has a launch window lasting until 19 November.
 Meanwhile in Pakistan we still concern ourselves with useless issues like what our Northern province should be called?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>