<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Writing on Butterfly Dream</title>
    <link>http://abijango.com/tags/writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Writing on Butterfly Dream</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://abijango.com/tags/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>RSS and other improvements</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-21-rss-and-other-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-21-rss-and-other-things/</guid>
      <description>I finally got RSS to work on the site, along with a few other under the hood improvements.
To point the RSS to your favourite Google Reader replacement, please go to the menu bar at the top -&amp;gt; RSS. Or point it directly to http://abijango.com/feed if you want.
I have some further enhancements in the pipeline, which will be rolling out sooner or later.
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Injustice for All: A Little South of Sanity</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-16-little-south-of-sanity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-16-little-south-of-sanity/</guid>
      <description>The laughter is the first thing that gets to most people. The shriekers, the wailers. And then those who snicker as if they know something you don&amp;rsquo;t. Makes more than a few wonder if it&amp;rsquo;s in fact the patients who know more than you. That they are privy to secrets that you are not. Maybe feeling that way is what drives most people away from places like this. An asylum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Injustice for All: Dusty Neighbourhood</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-14-dusty-neighbourhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-14-dusty-neighbourhood/</guid>
      <description>Flicking the cigarette and taking a swig from the half drunk cup of coffee, he sighed. Out came the smoke in misty curls. He half tried to make rings, failed miserably and gave up. He was never very good at that. Looking out the window to his scenic view, the first thing that you saw was the criss-crossed wires. Telephone wires, electricity wires, bloody everything else wires. Covered in dirt and bird shit and god knows what else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Injustice for All</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-02-injustice-for-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-02-injustice-for-all/</guid>
      <description>I have been writing short stories since I was very young. Most of them used to be nothing more than just childhood fiction. These days I am more interested in writing about certain aspects of my culture. Highlighting certain issues if you will.
The future posts that follow with the titles beginning with &amp;ldquo;Injustice for All&amp;rdquo;, will be part of short stories that are linked in one way or another; and where I try to fit together these disjointed stories about things that I want to highlight about my culture.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>