<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Star Wars on Butterfly Dream</title>
    <link>http://abijango.com/tags/star-wars/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Star Wars on Butterfly Dream</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://abijango.com/tags/star-wars/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How Boba Fett Escaped the Sarlacc Pit</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-23-boba-fetts-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-23-boba-fetts-escape/</guid>
      <description>Where a fan goes the extra mile:
 Stoefller submitted the diorama for French lego contest, along with a fantastical story that offers an alternate take on how Boba survived falling into the Sarlacc during Return of the Jedi.
 The detail is just astonishing.
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Madame Tussauds Star Wars Exhibition</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-04-madame-tussauds-star-wars-exhibition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-04-madame-tussauds-star-wars-exhibition/</guid>
      <description>On the back of so much Star Wars talk this week, here is some more, Madam Tussauds will open a Star Wars exhibition this year. Holy shit. Ok so since it is only a short walk from my office, I am probably wasting a lot of money there. DAMNIT! SHUTUP AND TAKE MY MONEY!
 Opening May 2015 Madame Tussauds London will take you to your favourite Star Wars scenes. Star Wars at Madame Tussauds will be a unique, immersive experience featuring 16 of the most famous heroes and villains in scenes from some of the most iconic moments featured in Star Wars Episodes I – VI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Brief History of Star Wars Canon</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-03-brief-history-of-star-wars-canon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-03-brief-history-of-star-wars-canon/</guid>
      <description>Star Wars has always had a special place in my heart. I write and tweet about it a lot. Maybe too much.
Nah!
After I had devoured the movies over and over again as a kid, I was left hanging. I wanted more. I wanted the Episodes I-III (OK maybe in hindsight I should have been careful what I wished for!), and there was nothing. I am sure it was much worse for the people for whom Star Wars had been a part of their lives since the late 70&amp;rsquo;s and 80&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The paintings of the Original Star Wars Trilogy</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-01-29-star-wars-paintings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-01-29-star-wars-paintings/</guid>
      <description>Talk about a childhood destroyed. I always thought they created this somehow, miniatures or something. But paintings? Wow!
 Matte paintings are fake sets that—most of the times—used to be made with plexiglass and oil paint. The artists used oversized panels to create the necessary detail that the camera needed to fool the audiences when the film was projected over the large surface of the theater screen. The paintings were combined with live action filmed to match the perspective of the painting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How the World Wars inspired the Millennium Falcon</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-21-millennium-falcon-and-the-world-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-02-21-millennium-falcon-and-the-world-wars/</guid>
      <description>The Millennium Falcon is no doubt some of the most recognizable nerd craft. The article traces the inspirations:
 The connections begin in the cockpit of the Falcon with its iconic greenhouse-style window. It was here that audiences first jumped to hyperspace, and from these famous viewports that Han Solo evaded Imperial ships in the asteroid field above Hoth. Thirty years earlier, this same style of cockpit was found flying aboard one of the most advanced bomber aircraft of World War II: The American B-29 Superfortress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars Episode VII script complete</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-01-20-star-wars-episode-7-script-complete/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-01-20-star-wars-episode-7-script-complete/</guid>
      <description>I am just hoping they don&amp;rsquo;t screw it up rushing it, but I guess Disney is just seeing the $$$$ and not much else.
That said, I can&amp;rsquo;t fucking wait!
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Official Star Wars Universe Just...Expanded</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-01-08-star-wars-expanded-universe/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-01-08-star-wars-expanded-universe/</guid>
      <description>So this just basically means that the new movies could draw their inspiration from some of the richest stories ever told in science fiction. Hell yes!
Here&amp;rsquo;s to hoping Disney picks up on the nerdgasms this has generated in the Star Wars community and decide to actually pick some of the most amazing story lines for the upcoming movies or animated series/films.
 So if by Episode VIII fans meet Grand Admiral Thrawn, all the better.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>So you like Star Wars?</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-06-star-wars-audition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-11-06-star-wars-audition/</guid>
      <description>So they are looking for two roles:
 They are a &amp;ldquo;street smart and strong&amp;rdquo; orphaned girl in her late teens and a &amp;ldquo;smart capable&amp;rdquo; man in his late teens or early 20s.
 So let&amp;rsquo;s all go and audition for these roles? If only&amp;hellip;.
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>