<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Butterfly Dream on Butterfly Dream </title>
      <generator uri="https://gohugo.io">Hugo</generator>
    <link>http://abijango.com/</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
    
    <updated>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 11:29:56 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Oldest Star Wars Fan</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-11-27-the-oldest-star-wars-fan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 11:29:56 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-11-27-the-oldest-star-wars-fan/</guid>
      <description>The first guy who ever realised what a success Star Wars was going to be. Just before the new movie comes out, and people still bashing Star Wars. Eat your hearts out haters!
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leonard Nimoy, dies at 83</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-27-leonard-nimoy-dies-at-83/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2015 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-27-leonard-nimoy-dies-at-83/</guid>
      <description>A legend dies. Seriously all, &amp;ldquo;Live long, and prosper!&amp;rdquo; \\// :(
 &amp;ldquo;Given the choice,&amp;rdquo; he wrote, &amp;ldquo;if I had to be someone else, I would be Spock.&amp;rdquo;
 You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Boba Fett Escaped the Sarlacc Pit</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-23-boba-fetts-escape/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-23-boba-fetts-escape/</guid>
      <description>Where a fan goes the extra mile:
 Stoefller submitted the diorama for French lego contest, along with a fantastical story that offers an alternate take on how Boba survived falling into the Sarlacc during Return of the Jedi.
 The detail is just astonishing.
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Sale of the Original Les Paul Black Beauty</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-23-original-les-paul-black-beauty-sale/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2015 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-23-original-les-paul-black-beauty-sale/</guid>
      <description>Holy shit! If only I had that kind of money. Gief!
 Les Paul&amp;rsquo;s personal 1954 Les Paul Custom &amp;ldquo;Black Beauty&amp;rdquo; sold to Indianapolis Colts owner Jim Irsay last night for $343,750.
 You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heroes Reborn Teaser</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-04-heroes-reborn-teaser/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-04-heroes-reborn-teaser/</guid>
      <description>I know what people say about Heroes, and no I won&amp;rsquo;t link to them. Who cares, I loved that show. And sadto see some of the original cast won&amp;rsquo;t be (and glad about some, I hated Claire&amp;rsquo;s character) but seriously watch the teaser, DAMN!
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Madame Tussauds Star Wars Exhibition</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-04-madame-tussauds-star-wars-exhibition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-04-madame-tussauds-star-wars-exhibition/</guid>
      <description>On the back of so much Star Wars talk this week, here is some more, Madam Tussauds will open a Star Wars exhibition this year. Holy shit. Ok so since it is only a short walk from my office, I am probably wasting a lot of money there. DAMNIT! SHUTUP AND TAKE MY MONEY!
 Opening May 2015 Madame Tussauds London will take you to your favourite Star Wars scenes. Star Wars at Madame Tussauds will be a unique, immersive experience featuring 16 of the most famous heroes and villains in scenes from some of the most iconic moments featured in Star Wars Episodes I – VI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix&#39;s Daredevil Teaser</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-04-netflix-daredevil-teaser/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-04-netflix-daredevil-teaser/</guid>
      <description>Daredevil heads to the tv screen! And it is bloody! Let&amp;rsquo;s hope it can make us forget all about that bad, bad movie. Yes you know which one I am talking about. You have just removed it from your memory.
You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Brief History of Star Wars Canon</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-03-brief-history-of-star-wars-canon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Feb 2015 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-02-03-brief-history-of-star-wars-canon/</guid>
      <description>Star Wars has always had a special place in my heart. I write and tweet about it a lot. Maybe too much.
Nah!
After I had devoured the movies over and over again as a kid, I was left hanging. I wanted more. I wanted the Episodes I-III (OK maybe in hindsight I should have been careful what I wished for!), and there was nothing. I am sure it was much worse for the people for whom Star Wars had been a part of their lives since the late 70&amp;rsquo;s and 80&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>50 Years of James Bond in Black Tie</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-01-30-fifty-years-of-bond-in-black-tie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-01-30-fifty-years-of-bond-in-black-tie/</guid>
      <description>What a really thourough investigation. Every single piece of clothing (no shoes sadly) calatalogued. The little nerd in me wants to do re-runs now (No Timothy Dalton, no way!).
 Though there are 28 dinner jackets, there are 29 shirts. George Lazenby wears two different ruffled shirts with the same dinner jacket in On Her Majesty’s Secret Service. Also, shoes are unfortunately missing from this infographic since they are rarely seen in the films.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zakk Wylde&#39;s Audio Gear</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-01-30-zakk-wyldes-audio-gear/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2015 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-01-30-zakk-wyldes-audio-gear/</guid>
      <description>Just shut up and take my money! If I had any that is. When this stuff comes out.
 Time will tell if Wylde will GIFD &amp;ndash; the acronym for &amp;ldquo;get it f&amp;ndash;ing done&amp;rdquo; that he and his BLS brethren have adopted as a motto.
 You can follow the author or shout at him on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The paintings of the Original Star Wars Trilogy</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2015-01-29-star-wars-paintings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2015-01-29-star-wars-paintings/</guid>
      <description>Talk about a childhood destroyed. I always thought they created this somehow, miniatures or something. But paintings? Wow!
 Matte paintings are fake sets that—most of the times—used to be made with plexiglass and oil paint. The artists used oversized panels to create the necessary detail that the camera needed to fool the audiences when the film was projected over the large surface of the theater screen. The paintings were combined with live action filmed to match the perspective of the painting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hong Kong Protests</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-09-29-hong-kong-protests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-09-29-hong-kong-protests/</guid>
      <description>Pro-democracy riots in Hong Kong. Note the similarities in the police actions and the reactions by the public to what is recently happening back home in Pakistan.
 The government urdged the protesters to end their sit-in demonstrations.
 Now why would people do that? Why is it that everywhere protests start &amp;ndash; Pakistan, UK, Hong Kong, elsewhere &amp;ndash; the authorities always have their ridiculous demands about not protesting? Why? Other than the authourities, who else benifits from not protesting?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chris Avellone&#39;s Gaming Rig</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-09-25-chris-avellones-gaming-rig/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-09-25-chris-avellones-gaming-rig/</guid>
      <description>Chris Avellone has been one of my childhood heroes since a friend of mine told me to go read the credits on our favourite game of all time, Fallout 2. Him and the other&amp;rsquo;s who made the amazing games over at Black Isle Studios just made my childhood amazing.
I now get to see a loot at what he uses as a gaming machine and his general desk and place of work/fun, great insight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For less than the price of a Hollywood movie</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-09-25-for-less-than-gravity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-09-25-for-less-than-gravity/</guid>
      <description>I wrote about India&amp;rsquo;s mission to Mars a while back, and now that spaceship has finally reached Mar&amp;rsquo;s orbit.
And all of this for less than the cost of what it took to make Gravity.
I think the New York Time&amp;rsquo;s article say&amp;rsquo;s it best though.
 One a shoestring, India sends orbiter to Mars on it&amp;rsquo;s first try.
 The trip cost India $74 million. Gravity on the other hand cost $100 million.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Censorship</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2014-03-24-censorship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2014 00:00:00 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2014-03-24-censorship/</guid>
      <description>Stories like these might sound sensational to you. Yes they are trying to paint a very bleak picture of our society and the kind of censorship that is prevalent. But it doesn&amp;rsquo;t change the fact that it is censorship.
 Today&amp;rsquo;s edition of The International New York Times was stripped of its cover story in Pakistan. Instead of seeing a lengthy report on &amp;ldquo;What Pakistan knew about bin Laden,&amp;rdquo; readers were greeted with an enormous section of white space that dominates the paper&amp;rsquo;s front page.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

