<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Link Post on Butterfly Dream</title>
    <link>http://abijango.com/tags/link-post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Link Post on Butterfly Dream</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://abijango.com/tags/link-post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyle Lambert&#39;s Art on an iPad</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-12-03-art-on-an-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-12-03-art-on-an-ipad/</guid>
      <description>I do experiment a little with Paper by 53 from time to time, actually this blog is sort of inspired by the man Michael Rose himself. I also sketch traditionally sometimes, have for many years; but looking at this, I am blown away. The patience and skill required to do something like this is just staggering. I wish one day I will have even a 10th of what Kyle has.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On India&#39;s Mission to Mars</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-22-indias-mission-to-mars/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-22-indias-mission-to-mars/</guid>
      <description>Our neighbours over in India have a plan to launch a space mission to Mars.
 The Mangalyaan probe was to have been launched as early as 28 October, but rough weather in the Pacific forced officials to delay the launch by a week. The unmanned mission has a launch window lasting until 19 November.
 Meanwhile in Pakistan we still concern ourselves with useless issues like what our Northern province should be called?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the NUST fines/issues</title>
      <link>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-01-on-this-new-nust-drama/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://abijango.com/post/2013-10-01-on-this-new-nust-drama/</guid>
      <description>I will start this by saying I attended E&amp;amp;ME College, NUST from 2003-2007. Hence, I have a very personal taste on these issues that everyone is talking about. To get it out of the way, EM&amp;amp;E College, NUST was a horrible place to study. Simply terri-bad. I have spent years of my life after my time there trying to erase it from my memory. Granted I met some of my best friends in that university, but most if not all friendships were based on our mutual hatred of EM&amp;amp;E and its administration.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>